sexmenu.org 2016-12-08

# Privacy – SexMenu.ORG

## Privacy Policy

SexMenu, Inc. (hereafter referred to as SexMenu) has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

## What this Privacy Policy Covers

This privacy policy covers SexMenu’s treatment of personally identifiable information collected by SexMenu through a website owned and operated by SexMenu.

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SexMenu does not own or control, or of persons that SexMenu does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which SexMenu’s websites link. Collection and Use of Personal Information

You can visit the websites of SexMenu without revealing any personal information. However, SexMenu needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase our products, register for an affiliate account, receive SexMenu newsletter, or use certain SexMenu services.

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. SexMenu will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member-s account, and to contact you regarding new products and services.

By accessing the services of SexMenu and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

## Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

SexMenu automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. SexMenu may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, SexMenu does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.

SexMenu also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and SexMenu assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

SexMenu may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of SexMenu to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information

SexMenu may otherwise disclose your personal information when: We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;

We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;

We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of SexMenu;

We find that your actions on our websites violate the SexMenu Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. Consent If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to SexMenu. If you have provided personal information to SexMenu and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify SexMenu at privacy@SexMenu.com.

## Security

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your SexMenu Information protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, SexMenu uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.

Further, SexMenu retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

SexMenu may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of SexMenu websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

## Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at privacy @SexMenu.com.

#### Incoming search terms:

  * Lovely indian pussy pics
  * photos school girls thailand sex
  * chiana sex photo gril com
  * South indian naked girl image
  * Hot indian masala girls image
  * photo japan chut 20015
  * unmature pussy photos
  * sex pinki bhabhi images
  * chikani women
  * aunties dirty picture images
  * Chainese beauti fucking photo
  * sex kartethue nange
  * pragnent anty sex images
  * Mhila nagi photo sacxe
  * beauty pregnant indian girl pussy photo
  * gand image india
  * yoni yoni big size girls breast
  * www chianasexphotos com
  * PUNJABI ASS GAAND WALLPEPAR
  * www chianasexphots com
